

Yuri Ramos Front-end Developer

My Objective

I am a person who is always looking for something new. I founded an online consulting firm in September 2014 aimed at changing the practices of the middle Health & Fitness in digital media and live new challenging experiences. Currently, working as front-end developer with 5 years of experience, working with WEBAPPS, Single-page Applications, Cross-browser responsive pages, Bootstrap and others. Focused on mastering the library React. JS + flux to develop isomorphic APPS.

Professional Experience

Front-end Developer [January 2015 - Currently]

Rio de Janeiro, Brazil

One of maintenance project leaders of the channels TV GLOBOSAT group. My role include create new features and hotfixes for every ongoing projects of GLOBOSAT, such as: Channel Sexy Hot, GNT, Multishow, among others.

Lead Developer [June 2014 - August 2015]

Remote Work

Act as leader of the new project CAPGOV, collaborating to create a new page into the context of current technologies and improving the position on google by SEO. Using drupal CMS as content manager.

Founder, Marketing Manager, Project Manager, Full-Stack Developer and BI [September 2014 - March 2016]

SoulFit was an online fitness consultancy that delivered to their customers a product encapsulated as "SoulFit Kit" that included:

Curitiba, Brazi
Rio de Janeiro, Brazi

Personalized Training; Personalized Diet; Ebooks made by us to help our customers achieve their goals. With minimum 3-months plan, we deliver to our customers feedbacks biweekly and monthly. Accordingly to their results if it's necessary we made changes in their diet and training plan.

Education

Computer Systems [August 2015 - Currently]

Federal University Fluminense- UFF

Computer Science [August 2010 - January 2015]

Federal University of Rio De Janeiro - UFRJ

Skills

Proficiency	Professional
HTML5/CSS	Programming
SASS/Gulp	UX/UI
Photoshop	TDD
DUD/COL	
PHP/SQL	Personal
Javascript Javascript	Personal Creative

Personal Information

Name Yuri Pereira Ramos

Birth June 12, 1991

Nacionality Brazilian

Nationality Rio de Janeiro

Languages English(fluent), Spanish (intermediate), Portuguese

Recently Projects

TesteDNA

Working developing the front-end of a startup e-Commerce in the field of parternity test and DNA tests.

Highlights

- Self-Didact
- Good Oratory
- Sociability
- Proactivity
- Ágile Development (Methodologies Scrum e Kanban)

Contact

Address Av. Prefeito Dulcidio Cardoso,

2500, bloco 2 apto 1501.

Phone +5521 97141-7218

Email yuri.pramos@gmail.com

Web www.yuriramos.com